Guide to the Tom Davis papers, 1994-2008
George Mason University Libraries
Special Collections and Archives, George Mason University
Tom Davis papers
1994-2008
George Mason University. Special Collections and Archives.
Davis, Thomas M., III
C0124
86 linear feet (64 boxes)
The collection contains issue files, legislative files, committee hearing files, thank-you letters, and constituent mail from his entire congressional career. There are also videotape cassettes, photographs, and many pieces of memorabilia. The collection will be closed to research until 2014.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no access restrictions.
Acquisition Information
Donated by Tom Davis in 2008.
Biographical Information
Elected in 1994, Davis began his career as chairman of the House Government Reform and Oversight Committee's Subcommittee on the District of Columbia. In January 2003, he was elected to chair the House Government Reform and Oversight Committee and was reappointed in January 2005 because of his outstanding work. He also served as the chairman of the National Republican Congressional Committee from 1998 to 2002. Davis retired from Congress in 2008.
Scope and Content
The collection contains issue files, legislative files, committee hearing files, thank-you letters, and constituent mail from his entire congressional career. There are also videotape cassettes, photographs, and many pieces of memorabilia.
Arrangement
Organized by subject.
Adjunct Descriptive Data
Related Material
Special Collections and Archives also holds many other personal paper collections from local, state, and national politicians.
Index Terms
Persons:
Davis, Thomas M., III.
Corporate Names:
United States. Congress. House.
Contents List
- Tom Davis papers, 1994-2008
  - GSA Warehouse proposal. Springfield, VA., 1974-1980 (Folder 1, Box 1)
  - BRAC (Base Realignment and Closure), July 2008 (Folder 2, Box 1)
    Final environmental assessment implementation of 2005 base realignment and closure (BRAC) recommendation 133 (Washington Headquarters Services) Fort Belvoir, Virginia. Tetra Tech, Inc. (includes CD with draft and final copy)
  - DoD (Department of Defense) setbacks, 2003-2004 (Folder 3, Box 1)
  - Fort Belvoir, 2006-2008 (Folder 4, Box 1)
  - Fort Belvoir, 2003-2007 (Folder 5, Box 1)
  - DAR (Defense access road) amendment, 2003-2005 (Folder 6, Box 1)
  - Woodlawn Road, 2004-2006 (Folder 7, Box 1)
  - Medicare in Virginia, 1997-1998 (Folder 8, Box 1)
  - H.R. 1354 mammography, 2001-2002 (Folder 9, Box 1)
  - BBRA (Balanced Budget Refinement Act of 1999) - Thomas questionnaire and information (Medicare), 2000 (Folder 10, Box 1)
  - Medicare RX, 2002 (Folder 11, Box 1)
  - NACDS (National Association of Chain Drug Stores) - Letter to speaker - H.R. 4680, 2000 (Folder 12, Box 1)
  - Competitive bidding, 2002 (Folder 13, Box 1)
  - SNF (Skilled nursing facilities) letter, 2002 (Folder 14, Box 1)
  - AHA (Advancing Health in America), 2001 (Folder 15, Box 1)
  - American Association of Nurse Anesthetists and American Society of Anesthesiologists, 2001 (Folder 16, Box 1)
  - Medicare MSAs (medical savings accounts), 1996 (Folder 17, Box 1)
  - Medicare private contracting, 1997-1998 (Folder 18, Box 1)
  - Stark II regulations, 1998 (Folder 19, Box 1)
  - Provider sponsored organizations (PSOs), 1997 (Folder 20, Box 1)
  - Medicare payment policy, 1997-1998 (Folder 21, Box 1)
  - Medicare and antitrust regulations, 1994-1995 (Folder 22, Box 1)
  - Medicare RX, 2001-2002 (Folder 23, Box 1)
  - Barr/Conyers antitrust proposal, 2002 (Folder 24, Box 1)
  - Virginia Retina Foundation, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - NIH (National Institutes of Health) appropriations, 2000-2001. (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - The Ricky Ray Hemophilia Relief Fund Act of 1997 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - HIPAA (Health Insurance Portability and Accountability Act), 1998-2001. (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Parkinson disease letter signed on, 2000-2001. (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Mens Health Act, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Mental Health Parity, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - H.R. 4600, Medical Malpractice Bill, 2002-2003. (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - BC/BS (Blue Cross/Blue Shield) Childrens Hospital issue, 2002-2003. (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Christian Science DHS (Department of Homeland Security) issue, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Cloning, stem-cell research, 2000-2001. (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - AIDS., 1997-2001. (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Patients Bill of Rights, 1998-2001. (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Medical records privacy, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Ovarian cancer, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Blood cancer money, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Duchenne Muscular Dystrophy, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Autism, 2001-2002. (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Breast cancer, 1998-2003. (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Health savings accounts, 1996-1999. (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Food Allergen Labeling and Consumer Protection Act, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - JWOD (Javits-Wagner-O'Day) program; RSA (Rehabilitation Services Administration) rule; Blind, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - T (testimony?) and PP bioterror hearing, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Hearing testimony before the Subcommittee on Technology and Procurement Policy, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - AIDS, 2008 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Information packets, 2007-2008 (Box 2, Folder 26)
    From multiple organizations: Virginia Space Grant Consortium, Arthritis Foundation, Food and Friends, The National Catholic Educational Association and the United States Conference of Catholic Bishops, IRS (Internal Revenue Service), National Association for the Education of Young Children, National Association of Health Underwriters, Space Exploration Alliance, American Council of the Blind, National Athletic Trainers ' Association
  - Information packets, 2007-2008 (Box 2, Folder 27)
    From multiple organizations: National Breast Cancer Coalition, NFB (National Federation of the Blind), (NSBA) National School Boards Association, PH.R. (Physicians for Human Rights), ABA (American Burn Association), Home School Legal Defense Association, Healthcare Leadership Council, American Diabetes Association, Health Professions and Nursing Education Coalition
  - Federal Trade Committee, Undated (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - CATO Institute, (Chip N.), 1995 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - USTR (United States Trade Representative), 1995 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - H.R. 1530, Abortions in military hospitals, June 13, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Real Estate Settlement Procedures Act (RESPA), 1994 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - NMUSA (National Museum of the United States Army), 1995 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - War Powers Resolution, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Legal/Tort reform, 1995 (2 folders) (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Contract with America, 1994-1995 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Common Sense Legal Reforms Act, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Government operations and federal employees, 1994-1995. (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Miscellaneous D.C., 1994 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Trade, NAFTA (North American Free Trade Agreement), GATT (General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade) (Chip N.?), 1995 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Legal reform, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - H.R. 1561; H.R. 1868, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Middle East, 1993-1995. (Box 3, Folder 6)
    Includes four publications: The Middle East, Politics and Development Jan. 95 and April 95; Middle East Affairs journal winter/spring 1995; Islam under siege June 1993. All published by the United Association for Studies and Research
  - USAID (United States Agency for International Development), 1995 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Bills introduced to Congress by the House Republicans., September 23, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    Bills include: The Citizen Legislature Act, The Common Sense Legal Reform Act, The Fiscal Responsibility Act, The Senior Citizens' Equity Act, The National Security Act, The American Dream Restoration Act, The Family Reinforcement Act, The Personal Responsibility Act, The Taking Back Our Streets Act, The Job Creation and Wage Enhancement Act
  - Miscellaneous, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Vietnamese Boat People, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Former Soviet Union, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Smith amendment, overseas family planning, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - China, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Constituent mail with response regarding multiple issues, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Constituent mail with response regarding the renaming of Reagan National Airport, 1997-1998 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Constituent mail with response regarding mostly transportation issues, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Constituent mail with response regarding mostly transportation issues, January-March 1998 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Constituent mail with response regarding multiple issues, April-June 1998 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Constituent mail with response regarding multiple issues, May-July 1998 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Constituent mail with response regarding multiple issues, July 1998 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Constituent mail with response regarding multiple issues, June-July 1998 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Constituent mail with response regarding H.R. 1415, PARCA (Patient Access to Responsible Care Act of 1997), July 8, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Constituent mail with response regarding multiple issues, July 1998 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Constituent mail with response regarding multiple issues, June-July 1998 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Constituent mail with response regarding Patients Bill of Rights Act of 1998 and H.R. 1415, PARCA (Patient Access to Responsible Care Act of 1997), July-August 1998 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Constituent mail with response regarding multiple issues, July-August 1998 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Constituent mail with response regarding multiple issues, July 1998 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Constituent mail with response regarding multiple issues, July 13-14, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Constituent mail with response regarding multiple issues, July 1998 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Constituent mail with response regarding multiple issues, July 1998 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Constituent mail with response regarding multiple issues, July-August 1998 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Constituent mail with response regarding Gay Rights, August 1998 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Constituent mail with response regarding multiple issues, August 6-10, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Constituent mail with response regarding multiple issues, August 5-6, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Constituent mail with response regarding multiple issues, August 4-5, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - CAFE (Corporate Average Fuel Economy) Markey vs. Hill-Terry Bill; H.R. 1506; H.R. 2927, 2007 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Fuel economy, 2000-2002 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Energy, 2003 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Nuclear energy policy, 2006 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Power lines, presentation print-out by the Office of Energy Projects, Federal Energy Regulatory Commission, February 2007 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Energy week, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Dominion Virginia Power transmission lines, 2006-2007 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Dubai loophole, 2008 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Telecommuting letters (from constituents), 2005 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Mt. Vernon zip code changes, Undated (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Pentagon child care center closing, 2004 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Prince William, GDLS (General Dynamics Land Systems Division), AAAV (Advanced Amphibious Assault Vehicle), 2003 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Quantico EIS (Environmental Impact Statement) / BRAC (Base realignment and closure), 2007 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Thomas Jefferson High School, 2002, 2006 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Tribes of Virginia. Thomasina E. Jordan Indian Tribes of Virginia Federal Recognition Act, February 16, 2007 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Vienna franchising issue. (Video/Cable TV franchising), November 2005 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Chesapeake Crescent, 2007-2008 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Vienna Post Office, 2004-2005 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - D.C. Vote Bill. (Chairman's remarks at the D.C. Voting Rights Summit), January 25, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - DoD (Department of Defense) building standards, 2002-2005 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - DoL (Department of Labor) transit benefit, 2002-2006 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Fairfax County Board letters, 2006 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - FEMA (Federal Emergency Management Agency) and Virginia flooding, July-August 2006 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - GAO (Government Accountability Office) COLA (Cost of Living Allowances), 2006-2007 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Goshen Dam, 1997-2007 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - GSA (General Services Administration) Franconia warehouse. (Fort Belvoir), 2006-2007 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Thomas Jefferson High School. (ASTRA (Alliance for Science & Technology Research in America)), 2007-2008 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Memorandum of agreement on the transfer of the Lorton Correctional Complex out of Federal ownership, 2001 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Woodglen Dam, 2006 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Lorton Correctional Complex, 2001 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Correspondence, letters from Virginia government, 2005-2008 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Telegraph Road (Fort Belvoir), 2002 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Vienna Post Office, 2004-2005 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Northern Virginia transportation tour, September 12-13, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Tysons tunnel petitions, 2006-2007 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Dulles Corridor Metrorail Project, 2007-2008 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Dulles rail and Tysons tunnel, 2006-2007 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Rail to Dulles, 2003-2007 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Dulles, 2007-2008 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Fort Belvoir BRAC (Base Realignment and Closure), EIS (Environmental Impact Statement) public meeting, draft EIS, March-April 2007 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Thomas Jefferson Institute for Public Policy, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Lorton Correctional Complex, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Foretich, et al. v. United States. (Elizabeth Morgan case), 1997 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Elizabeth Morgan case, 1994-1995 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Elizabeth Morgan, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - The Elizabeth Morgan case, 1994-1995 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Getting federal computers ready for 2000, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - H.R. 1855, Elizabeth Morgan case, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Elizabeth Morgan case correspondence, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Morgan Bill, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Elizabeth Morgan case, 1995-1996 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Elizabeth Morgan case, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - NVRPA (Northern Virginia Regional Park Authority) special events centers, October 27, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - GSA (General Services Administration) FSS (Federal Supply Service), Undated (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - FCC (Federal Communications Commission) CWI (Cable and Wireless, Inc.) issue, October 31, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - US-Israel Science and Technology Commission, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - GSA (General Services Administration), PWC (Prince William County) per diem, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Army prepositioned stocks-afloat program, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence, speeches, reports (Chip N.), 1994-1996 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Elizabeth Morgan case, 1994-1995 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Information Technology Working Group, 1995-1996 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - World Congress 1998 information technology, June 22-25, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - World Congress 1998; D.C., 1997-1998 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Mike Thompson. (Thomas Jefferson Institute for Public Policy, Alan Merten, GMU), 1997 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - AFCEA (Armed Forces Communications and Electronics Association) talking points; Y2K, ITWG, information and technology related papers, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Big LEO (low-Earth orbit), 1997 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - 14th Street Bridge, October 22, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Dulles Rail miscellaneous, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Brookings, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - H.R. 1534 Property Rights, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - American International Airways Detroit Flight Standards Office, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Constituent mail with response regarding federal funding of abortions, August 31, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Constituent mail with response regarding federal funding of abortions, August 31, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Constituent mail with response regarding President Clinton impeachment, August 1998 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Constituent mail with response regarding H.R. 3230 to amend Title X Parental Notification Act of 1998, August 31, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Constituent mail with response regarding multiple issues, August 31-September 4, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Constituent mail with response regarding Healthcare, August 31 and September 3, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Constituent mail with response regarding multiple issues, August 31-September 10, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Constituent mail with response regarding interstate waste., September 3-10, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Constituent mail with response regarding Medicare, August 14 and September 9, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Constituent mail with response regarding estate tax, September 8, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Constituent mail with response regarding H.R. 2094 B.E.A.C.H. Bill, September 8, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Constituent mail with response regarding multiple issues, September 8-18, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Constituent mail with response regarding multiple issues, September 14-18, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Constituent mail with response regarding Medicare and abortion, September 22-23, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Constituent mail with response regarding interstate waste and estate tax, September 14-28, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Constituent mail with response regarding multiple issues, September 22, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Constituent mail with response regarding multiple issues, September 1998 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Constituent mail with response regarding multiple issues, September 1998 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Legislative Digest; Floor Prep; Fact Sheet, October 24, 1995-September 24, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Eyegaze, eye-tracking system, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Endangered Species Act, 1995-1996 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - EPA (Environmental Protection Agency) / ESA (Endangered Species Act) flood, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - SCI Consulting, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - U.S.G.S. (U.S. Geological Survey), 1995 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - U.S.G.S. (U.S. Geological Survey), 1995 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Contractor conversion, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Base technologies, 1996-1997 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Highway 1, miscellaneous technology issues, 1996-1997 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - H.R. 1022, February 23, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - AWIPS (Advanced Weather Interactive Processing System) & DeGeorge, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Blue Plains, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Miscellaneous, Cryptek, endangered species, balanced budget constitutional amendment report, 1995-1998 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Baseball strike, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Telecommunications Act of 1996 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - DoD (Department of Defense), Development of the P-3 / Pioneer Project, 1994-1995 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Census information for Congress, Census 2000, 1996-1998 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Encryption, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Wireless competition report for the state of Virginia, Undated (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Computer security, 1997-1998 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Cryptek, February 10, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - PTO (Patent and Trademark Office) compensatory time, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Baseball Strike, 1994-1995 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - NVTC (Northern Virginia Transportation Commission); EPA (Environmental Protection Agency)., 1996 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - 1996 election, Clinton, Whitewater; Balanced Budget Reconciliation Act of 1995 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Military; Environmental Report Card, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - PTO (Patent and Trademark Office) Space Procurement, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Technical standards for radio, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Constituent mail with response regarding credit unions, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Constituent mail with response regarding multiple issues, 1997-1998, bulk April 23, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Correspondence (arranged alphabetically), 2001-2003 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Constituent mail with response regarding multiple issues, April 1998 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Constituent mail with response regarding health care issues, April 1998 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Constituent mail with response regarding multiple issues, April 1-13, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Constituent mail with response regarding multiple issues, April 1998 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Constituent mail with response regarding health care issues, April 1998 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Prison populations, Department of Justice, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Branch Davidians, Waco, TX, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Wireless. (Telecommunications Act of 1996), 1996-1997 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Subcommittee on Human Resources and Intergovernmental Relations, TMO statements, 1994-1995 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Line item veto, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - John Goodman from Associated Sound Services Inc., labor issue, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - LOCK (Lock Out Child Krime), Protection from Sexual Predators Act, H.R. 713, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Juvenile Crime, July-August 1995 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Campaign finance reform, H.R. 2072, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - National Night Out, July 20, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Jones Act Waiver, Too Much Fun, H.R. 1599, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Dr. Charles Nasem, ICCMHS (International Commercial Center for Manufactured Housing Systems), 1997 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - International Trade Administration, June 1996 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Drug Legalization, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Gift ban, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Waco, Ruby Ridge, 1994-1995 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Lobbying, H.R. 3078, March 13, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Product Liability Reform, March 1996 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Pragma Systems Corporation, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Au Pair Program, H.R. 2767, December 1995-January 1996 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Yvonne McCall for Fairfax County School Board At-Large endorsement, October 1995 (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - H.R. 1599, H.R. 500, H.R. 104, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Frebon International Corporation, (Bonnie Horner), July 1995 (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Virginia Railway Express, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - Hate crimes, 1993-1995 (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - FEMA (Federal Emergency Management Agency) church burning arson report, 1996-1997 (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - H.R. 994, Small Business Growth and Administrative accountability Act, 1995-1996 (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - Bailey's Community Center, April 8, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - Virginia DWI (Driving While Intoxicated) information, 1995-1996 (Box 10, Folder 32)
  - H.R. 588 Marion Walsh Drunk Driving Act of 1995 (Box 10, Folder 33)
  - Constituent mail with response regarding multiple issues, March-April 1998 (Box 10, Folder 34)
  - Constituent mail with response regarding multiple issues, April 1-3, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 35)
  - Constituent mail with response regarding Credit Unions, April 2, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 36)
  - Federal and District of Columbia Government Real Property Act of 2005 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Statements by Davis (Congressional Record, multiple events in Fairfax, honor of peers) 1 of 4, 2002-2005 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Statements by Davis (Congressional Record, multiple events in Fairfax, honor of peers) 2 of 4, 2003-2005 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Statements by Davis (Congressional Record, multiple events in Fairfax, honor of peers) 3 of 4, 2002-2005 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Statements by Davis (Congressional Record, multiple events in Fairfax, honor of peers) 4 of 4, 2003-2005 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - From Fairfax County, 1999-2000 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Old speeches, 1997-1998 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Lorton Correctional Complex in Lorton, VA, GSA (General Services Administration) Report to Congress, January 3, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 8)